Guide to the Duane Family Papers 1700-1945 MS 179
New-York Historical Society
- Series IV: Bound Volumes, 1754-1843, undated
  - Daybook, James Duane, 1783-1787 (Box BV Duane Family, Volume 9)
  - Duanesburgh Christ Church Register of Baptisms 1795-1812/Record of legal cases, 1755-1769, 1760's-1790's (Box BV Duane Family, Volume 10)
  - New York Court Dockets, 1769-1787 (Box BV Duane Family, Volume 11)
  - Extracts from the journals of James Duane, undated (Box BV Duane Family, Volume 12)
  - Letterbook, 1770-1795 (Box BV Duane Family, Volume 13)
  - James Duane journals, 1765-1789 (Box BV Duane Family, Volume 14)
  - Duane Family Genealogy, undated (Box BV Duane Family, Volume 15)
  - Register of lands in three parts: 1. Duaneburg; 2. Lands affected by the New Hampshire Claims; 3. Detached Lands, 1765-circa 1790's (Box BV Duane Family, Volume 16)
    Separated Materials
    Two oversized items ("Map of the Subdivision of the Great or Hardenburgh's Patent" and "Plan of Duanesburgh") were removed from this volume and will be found in Duane OS Folder 20.
  - Cookbook, Eliza Duane, 1843 (Box BV Duane Family, Volume 17)
  - Cookbook, undated (Box BV Duane Family, Volume 18)
  - Cookbook, circa 1850's? (Box BV Duane Family, Volume 19)
  - Cookbook, 1857 (Box BV Duane Family, Volume 20)
  - Cookbook, undated (Box BV Duane Family, Volume 21)
  - Cookbook, undated (Box BV Duane Family, Volume 22)
  - Loose recipes, undated (Box BV Duane Family, Volume 23)